indabamusic.com 2013-05-14

# Indaba Music

This page load seems to be taking a long time.   
If the page does not load within 5 seconds, try reloading. 

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

Indaba Media, LLC takes privacy and data protection issues seriously. This Privacy Policy describes certain data collected on the Indaba Music Web Site and what we do with it. Keeping this information private and secure is very important to Indaba. Indaba reserves the right to make changes or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Changes take effect when they are posted on the Indaba Music Web Site.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@indabamusic.com.

**Collection**

You can browse certain areas of the Indaba Music Web Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States.

We DO NOT provide your personal identifying information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services, and we may aggregate it for other purposes without identifying individual users.

**Use**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to enable you to share it with other members of the Indaba Music community through Profiles and Sessions or other collaboration on the Indaba Music Web Site. Our intent in collecting this information is to provide you with a useful, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use;
  * customize, measure, and improve our services and the Indaba Music Web Site's content and layout;
  * tell you about service updates and promotional offers that we may occasionally offer; and compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

Additionally, Indaba will collect personal information in the course of processing a payment transaction for the purchase of goods or services, special offers or special features through the Indaba Music Web Site. The personal information we acquire in processing such purchases varies according to the nature of the purchase. It may include, for example, your name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address and shipping address. Indaba uses the information collected to fulfill your purchase and otherwise facilitate the delivery of the goods or services and for no other purpose.

While your credit card information is collected at the time of purchase, only the last four digits are stored on Indaba's server. Credit card information is sent directly to the Quantum Gateway Website Payment Processing secure server, a fully PCI-compliant, PCI Level 1 Certified Payment Gateway solution (www.quantumgateway.com) and that is where it is safely held. To read Quantum Gateway's Privacy Policy, please visit the Quantum Gateway website referenced above. Indaba collects personal information through a secure server that features the latest encryption technology.

**Our Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that Users have violated copyright or other applicable law, or to protect our Users' rights or safety.

We may also share your personal information with: 

  * other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information; (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service)
  * law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity.

**Using Information from the Indaba Music Web Site**

The Indaba Music Web Site enables Users to share personal information and digital files in order to network with one another and collaborate. We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information and therefore we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your collaborative partners before entering into a Session and choosing to collaborate with others. Any information you input in your Profile will be visible to other members of the Indaba Music community and also to non-registrants who are not logged in should you choose to make such information public using the functionality available when editing your profile.

You agree to use User information only for: 

  * Indaba Music Session-related purposes that are not unsolicited commercial messages;
  * using services offered through the Indaba Music Web Site (e.g. Clip sharing, Session collaboration), or
  * other purposes that a User expressly chooses and consents to.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain pages of the Indaba Music Web Site to help analyze our web page flow, customize our services, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * We offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies.
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Indaba Music Web Site.

**No spam, spy ware or spoofing**

We and our Users do not tolerate spam, spy ware, or spoofing. You are not licensed to add other Indaba Music Web Site Users, even a User who has collaborated with you, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our Terms of Use.

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your Indaba Music Web Site password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account according to our Terms of Use. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Indaba Media, LLC and change your password.

**Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information**

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by logging into the Indaba Music Web Site. We will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible

**Security**

Your information is stored on servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other Users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Third Parties**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to third parties different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Indaba Media, LLC does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**Using Information from the Indaba Music Web Site**

The Indaba Music Web Site enables Users to share personal information and digital files in order to network with one another and collaborate. We encourage you to disclose your privacy practices and respect the privacy of other users. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information and therefore we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your collaborative partners before entering into a Session and choosing to collaborate with others. Any information you input in your Profile will be visible to other members of the Indaba Music community and also to non-registrants who are not logged in.
